Look, your problem is not Wil Wheaton.
Your problem is the way you treated Amy.
(Sheldon:)Problem is I'm out of tea.
(Penny:)Come on, someone insulted your girlfriend,
you just let him do it?
(Penny:)Thought you Texas guys stood up
for your womenfolk.
Oh, Penny, please.
(Sheldon:)Think I've evolved
beyond my simple rustic upbringing.
(Amy:)Sorry.
(Sheldon:)On the other hand, that low-down polecat
done wronged my woman.
(Penny:)Welcome to Long Island, Tex.
(Sheldon:)Amy deserves better.
(Howard:)You know,
when we buy the Planters Deluxe Mix...
(Sheldon:)...she eats all the Brazil nuts
so I don't have to look at them.
(Sheldon:)She's a unique blend of saint and squirrel.
Yup, that she is. Here you go.
(Sheldon:)I'm a callous egomaniac.
She's gonna leave me.
- No, she won't.
- No, she won't. I'm great.